bdspot.com 2017-11-10

# Privacy Policy

**_OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY_**

BDSPOT value their customers and respect their privacy.  
This privacy policy describes the personal information we may collect from you, the purposes for which we collect it, how we use it and when we may share it with third parties. This Policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect, use and disclose your information when you provide it to us on [www.bdspot.com](http://www.bdspot.com/) BDSPOT will not collect, use or disclose your personal information other than in compliance with this Policy.

By using the [www.bdspot.com](http://www.bdspot.com/) website and/or making online purchases of products, you agree to the terms and conditions of BDSPOTâ€™s Policy. If our Policy changes in the future, we will notify our customers and website users of any such changes by posting an updated policy on our website. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective.

**_OUR PRIVACY POLICY_**  
â€¢ What kind of information does BDSPOT collect?   
â€¢ For what purposes does BDSPOT collect my information?   
â€¢ Does BDSPOT share my information with third parties?   
â€¢ What are cookies and how does BDSPOT use cookies on its site?   
â€¢ How long is personal information retained?   
â€¢ How is personal information secured?

**_What kind of information does BDSPOT collect?_**  
We may collect personal information from you when you save or otherwise provide your personal information to us, such as by setting up a user account and password, logging in as a registered user of  _www.bdspot.com_ searching for a product, placing an order for a product, providing information in your account (and you might have more than one, if you've used more than one e-mail address when shopping with us), communicating with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise or if you complete an entry form to participate in a contest, promotion or survey. As a result of these actions, you might supply us with personal information, such as your name, e-mail and postal addresses, phone number(s), credit card information, names of people to whom purchases have been shipped, including address and telephone numbers, product interest information and financial information and in certain circumstances, your opinions and individual preferences.

BDSPOTâ€™s website is intended for use by adults. BDSPOT does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. Those under age 13 should not use BDSPOTâ€™s website or provide BDSPOT with any personal information. Where personal information is knowingly collected from 13 to 16 year old BDSPOT will not disclose it nor transfer it to third parties without parental consent.

**For what purposes does BDSPOT collect my information?**  
BDSPOT may use your personal information to (i) process your order and to answer questions about the status of your order; (ii) send you or your friends, relatives or associates, products that you have ordered; (iii) maintain contact with you and provide you with ongoing personalized service; (iv) communicate with you (via e-mail, post or otherwise) and provide you with promotional materials and additional information regarding our products, services, surveys, contests, promotions and special offers; (v) help us learn more about your shopping preferences; and (vi) conduct marketing and performance research, to assist us in measuring our customer service, benchmarking our performance and to help us improve our shopping experiences and product offerings. As provided below, you may always choose not to receive promotional materials or marketing information.

**_Does BDSPOT share my information with third parties?_**  
We may use a third party service provider to conduct our contests, surveys, promotions or special offers; that company will be prohibited from using our usersâ€™ personal information for any other purpose. We will not share the personal information you provide through our contests, surveys, promotions or special offers with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

We do not sell or rent your personal information to non-affiliated third parties except as permitted by law or as outlined within this Policy. However, in the event of a sale of all or substantially all of our business or another similar transaction, we may transfer or disclose your personal information to a purchaser or prospective purchaser, who may collect, use and disclose such information for the purposes of evaluating the proposed transaction or operating and managing the affairs of the acquired business, or for other purposes identified in this Policy. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

We may transfer personal information to non-affiliated third parties, such as a shipping company to fulfill orders, a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services and an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf,pursuant to agreements that prohibit the third parties from using or disclosing the personal information other than for the purpose of processing and which impose security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information.

The collection, use, and disclosure of information contemplated in this Policy may involve a transfer of the information to jurisdictions located outside your country of residence that may not have equivalent laws and rules regarding personally identifiable information. By way of example, this may happen if one of our service providers is located in a country outside your home country. In these cases, we will take steps to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law, and as necessary to protect the property, interests and rights of BDSPOT

BDSPOTâ€™s website may contain links to websites operated by third parties. These websites may collect your personal information. This Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties and BDSPOT does not assume any responsibility for, and by using this website and/or accessing a third partyâ€™s website from this website you release BDSPOT of any responsibility for, the actions, practices and omissions of third parties. Please check the privacy policy at each site you visit.

**_What are cookies? How does BDSPOT use cookies on its site?_**  
We may use â€œcookiesâ€ to track your preferences and activities on the 

 _www.bdspot.com_

 website. Cookies are small data files transferred to your computerâ€™s hard-drive by a website. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our site. They keep a record of your preferences making your subsequent visits to the site more efficient. Cookies may store a variety of information, including, the number of times that you access a site, registration information and the number of times that you view a particular page or other item on the site. The use of cookies is a common practice adopted by most major sites to better serve their clients. Most browsers are designed to accept cookies, but they can be easily modified to block cookies; see your browser's help files for details on how to block cookies, how to know when you have received cookies and how to disable cookies completely. You should note, however, that without cookies, some of the website's functions will not be available, and the user will lose some of the benefits of the site.

**_CAN I TELL A FRIEND ABOUT BDSPOT PRODUCTS?_**  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our products, we will ask you for your friendâ€™s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. BDSPOT stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at _info@bdspot.com_

**_SOCIAL MEDIA WIDGETS_**  
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook button [and Widgets, such as the Twitter button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**_HOW CAN I ACCESS OR CHANGE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION, WITHDRAW MY CONSENT?_**  
BDSPOT will ensure that the personal information it collects is as accurate, complete, and up-to-date as is necessary for the purposes for which it is to be used. You are entitled to request access to and correction or deletion of your personal information collected by us. In order to make such a request, please contact our privacy officer.

Privacy Officer  
info@bdspot.com

please note that you can also withdraw your consent at any time by communicating with our privacy officer as provided above. We will respond to your request for access within 30 days.

**_How long is personal information retained?_**  
We will keep your personal information only as long as is reasonably necessary for the purposes described in this Policy or such longer period as may be required by applicable law.

**_How is personal information secured?_**  
We have adopted appropriate measures to ensure the confidentiality of personal information and to safeguard personal information against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification, in light of, among other things, the sensitivity of the information and the purposes for which it is to be used. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and we do not store sensitive credit card data on our systems once the payment transaction has completed. Furthermore, each and every BDSPOT employee, mandatory or agent must abide by this Policy. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at  _info@bdspot.com_
